Guide to the Davenport College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2006 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Davenport College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1964-2006 maintained by the dean
1960-2012
RU 223
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
101.58
(151 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Davenport College, Yale University.
Davenport College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-F-1 (YRG 13-F-1), Records of the dean of Davenport College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Davenport College, Yale University.
College students; Davenport College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1964, Accession 1969-A-003
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1965, Accession 19ND-A-273
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Withdrawals
- Student record cards for the Classes of 1964-1969, Accession 19ND-A-278 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
  - Class of 1964
  - Class of 1965
  - Class of 1966
  - Class of 1967
  - Class of 1968
  - Class of 1969
- Student records for the Class of 1966, Accession 19ND-A-274
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
- Student records for the Class of 1967, Accession 19ND-A-275
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-276
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
- Student records for the Class of 1969, Accession 19ND-A-277
- Student records for the Class of 1970, Accession 19ND-A-279
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
- Student records for the Class of 1971, Accession 19ND-A-280
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2047
- Student records for the Class of 1972, Accession 1977-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
- Student records for the Class of 1973, 1969-1973; Accession 1978-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
- Student records for the Class of 1974, Accession 1979-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
- Student records for the Class of 1975, Accession 1980-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
- Student records for the Class of 1976, Accession 1981-A-036
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
- Student record cards for the Classes of 1973-1976, Accession 1984-A-041
  - Class of 1973
  - Class of 1974
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
- Impounded student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, Accession 1975-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1977, Accession 1982-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  Arranged alphabetically by last name
- Student records for the Class of 1978, Accession 1983-A-064
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
- Student records for the Class of 1979, Accession 1984-A-042
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
- Student records for the Class of 1980, Accession 1985-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
- Student records for the Class of 1981, Accession 1987-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1982, Accession 1988-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1983, Accession 1989-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1984, Accession 1990-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Classes of 1985-1986, Accession 1992-A-079
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  Arranged by class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Class of 1985
    - Withdrawals (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Class of 1986
    - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1993-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1994-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1995-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1996-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1991, Accession 2001-A-076
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Non-graduates, 1987-1991
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 2002-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1993, Accession 2003-A-030
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1994, Accession 2004-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Non-grads
- Student records for the Class of 1995, Accession 2007-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Non-grads
- Student records for the Class of 1996, Accession 2008-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - NON-GRADUATES
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1993-1997; Accession 2009-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - NON -GRADUATES
- Student records for the Classes of 1998-1999, 1994-1999; Accession 2011-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Class of 1998
    - NON-GRADUATES
  - Class of 1999
    - NON-GRADUATES
- Student records for the Class of 2000, 1993-2012; Accession 2012-A-096
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2087
  - Non-Graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2001, 1996-2001; Accession 2014-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Non-Graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 1998-2002; Accession 2015-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Non-Graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2003, Accession 2016-A-006
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2078 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
  - Non-Graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2004, Accession 2017-A-023
  Restricted until January 1, 2080
  - Non-graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2005, Accession 2018-A-025
  Restricted until January 1, 2081
  - Non Graduates
- Student records for the Class of 2006, Accession 2019-A-0008
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
  - Abrams, Daniel Seth (deceased), 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albert, Marissa Lauren, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Austin, Paige Parker, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Brianne Noel, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baller, Erica Berlin, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barr, Jordan Learner, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beauchman, Jihad Frederick, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Berv, David Everett, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bice, Sezgi, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brooks, Christopher, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cervantes, Vanessa Michelle, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chen, Christopher Wen-Chien, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chen, Xueying, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cheng, Jessie, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chow, Conroy Locke, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Christakis, Theodore Jonathan, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cohen, Tania Gabrielle, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conde, Mario Rodrigo, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cruz, Johany Jennifer, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Craig, Zachary Edward, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dadok, Alexander Thomas, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dalby, Owen Benjamin, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Emerson Stanley, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dayton, Andrew Rockefeller, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dizon, Karlo Isaias Jorge, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Nguyen, Vicky V., 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Doggett, Rebecca Annabel, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dohrmann, Elizabeth Howell, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dunlop, Lisa Campbell, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ellis, Hirotaka Kanai, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Espinosa, Samuel M, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ferendez, Jennifer Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Fishman, Peter Scott, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Gage, Rosanna Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Garcia, Bobby Allen, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Gelfand, Yevgeny, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Gillece, Marly Megan, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Goldberg, Jordan Adam, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Greene, Katie Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Gryll, Sarah Michelle, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Gudzowski, Milosz Karol, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Hartmann, Justin Peter, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Hazel, Margaret McEntee, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Hedrick, Matthew Ryan, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Hollis, Mary Catherine, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Holub, Robert Franklin, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Huguenin, Patrick Emile, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Huh, Yejin, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Jackson, Tianna Elise, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Jacobson, Daniel Frederick, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Jahanbakhsh, Bahram, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Jeanty, Laura Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Jones, Miranda Ferriss, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Kallaugher, Daniel McKeown, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Kaplan, Amy Beth, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Karlsen, Eivind Peter, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Kenagy, Susanne Day, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Shaffer, Alan, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Kovary, Meridith Nicole, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Laskow, Sarah Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Lee, Janet YiMan, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Leon, Brienne R., 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Lopes, Renee Carla, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - McDaniel, Michael Gregory, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McKain, Jodi-Ann Janel, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Main, Galen Eileen, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Maswoswe, Tanaka Jonathan Justice, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Matzner-Gore, Greta Nicole, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mehra, Chaitanya, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mix, Monica Clare, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Nakashima, Emily Anne, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Needle, Cory Aaron, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Oh, Steven Changsuk, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Oliver, Lily Rosenblatt, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ortega, Jamie Lyn, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pastrana, Isaac, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Perretta, Donato Joseph, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Quintana, Megan Theresa, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rasmussen, Erick Karl, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ray, Jason Wilton, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rees, William Trevor, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reid, Amelia Jean, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Remus, Jeb Edward, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rohde, Matthew Chrisopher, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Romero, Michael Paul, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Schaul-Yoder, Anneke Heverlee, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Schwarz, Jonathan Lassally, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Shumate, Erika Joy, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sim, Sana, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Simpson, Amelia Fabe, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Simpson, Lauren A., 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Robert Kingsley, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Staub, Benjamin Irving, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Swanson, Jonathan Wesley, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sweetnam, Elizabeth Adele Z., 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Taft-McPhee, Lauren Emily, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Taroutina, Maria, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Taylor, Shomari Akil, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Tharoor, Kanishk Vishokan Bharat, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Thomson, Phillippa Charlotte L., 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tilton, Alexander Freund, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Tran, Tracy Caroline, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Treadgold, Jonathan Stephen, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Trudeau, Rachel Grandison, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Warren, Alice Sterling, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Wheelwright, Emily Stevens, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Wilkinson, Brice Alexander, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Winn, Lucy Liddell, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Yang, Yan, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Yi, Ivanna Sang Een, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Zelinsky, Aaron Simchs, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Non-graduates
    - Jordan, Robert E. Hand, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - McGerr, Katherine Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)